Hi, my name is Vincent, and today we're
going to talk about one of my projects.
This is called IT pal. So I by coding this
project,
and right now I want to put it back to
the, to Figma to make the design
tweaks.
And then I will build the system for that.
To do that, I open the Figma
file.
I open the plugin, it's called
HTML to Design. So you can import
the URL on a screenshot, and then the
plugin will
convert it to the design Figma file.
So as you can see, we have the design file
here. I used this plugin to do
that.
Then
I need design tokens. First of all,
I need a rule, so I, I, I search on
internet. So someone
already find the, the system rule. So
primitive token, semantic token,
responsive token. So res-- semantic token
and responsive token, those
I will
inherit
it from the primitive tokens.
So I will use
the LLM agents. So then you can see that
by an image, please create a JSON file for
this token,
and then I have
the, the JSON file.
Back to the Figma, I use the plugin, it's
called Tok- Token
Studio for Figma.
I load, I load up the JSON file
I me-- I just mentioned,
and then let's see what, what we got.
And then I click Export Style
and Variable to Figma.
And voilà, this is what we have. We have
primitive
token, semantic dark, responsive desktop,
responsive mobile.
And semantic dark and responsive desktop
will,
will be inherited from primitive
token.
Next, I want to
change the design after I make the tweaks.
For example, for the product page,
I always make the change here,
and in the new designs, I change the batch
considerations.
And you can see it right now
in the light side, it's still considered a
different color.
And, and right click, I copy the link on
the Figma. I
paste it
to the agent and then, "Hey,
can you implement, implement the
new design
of the product page? Follow
the rules I
define."
And then you can see that
the LLM, the agents will connect to the
Figma MCP server. So you, you need to
open that bridge.
This is the s--
uh, this is the rules
when I, when I... This is the rule files,
and I just, I just told
the LLM that just follow the spec from the
general markdown file.
Okay, and after a while, so this is a new
page of a rover page. You can see that
it totally
different from the old versions, so and
especially for the considering patch, it
totally
have a new color.
Here, here it is, the new design is in
the Figma.
Okay, thank for listening.